"In his sleep,
everything is forgotten."
"But when he opened his eyes,
and his thoughts caught up with him,"
"he remembered that..."
"...outside the cabin,
beyond the surf,"
"above the indifferent sky,
that fucker was lying in wait."
-"The comet..."
-Honey? God, it's pretentious.
-But it's...
-Well, that's what I think.
-Pompous.
-Well, it's a novel.
-I was going for sublime.
-Right...
-How are you today?
-Please, can you get him out of here?
-Sure?
-I don't want him here. Thank you.
Let's go, Shrimpy!
-The cat.
-The cat?
Why is there a cat in the ward, Mom?
His name is Shrimpy.
He comes to you when it's time.
-It's not time yet.
-That's what I keep saying.
Shrimpy seems to disagree.
A cigarette would really hit the spot
right about now.
Mom!
It's not funny.
I'll keep reading.
Have you called John?
No. Why would I?
-Has he called you?
-No, why would he?
-Because you're his mother.
-You're his older brother.
So you call him.
-I'm going to keep reading.
-Call him for my sake. Please.
Quiet!
Try to get some rest, Mom.
"The doctor had said
it was not looking good, it was..."
"...really not looking good."
You know what, I'll...
I'm going to skip ahead.
-This is very...
-Pick a lighter passage.
I'm going to skip to
the next chapter.
"The sea lay glassy,
beneath the rocks.
It was calm.
Much too quiet."
Get the fuck out of my life!
I don't need you anymore.
Two, I fucking hate you,
you fucking bitch!
And three, fuck you!
Sorry, I don't get it.
Why does he say that?
He doesn't hate her at all.
He wants her back, right?
Why do I have to wear this?
So don't wear it. I promised
the Americans the tape tonight.
Why does it matter?
I'm not gonna land this anyway.
Don't say that!
You never know what audition
will be your ticket across the pond.
You want to get there, right?
Yes... well, doesn't everyone?
That doesn't mean...
Yeah, but not everyone has  it  .
Igor? I get that you're nervous.
It's a big studio, hot-shot director.
But they asked to see you.
They asked you to record yourself.
I didn't call and hassle them.
They've seen you, they like you.
Remember that. You're fantastic!
-No, I'm not.
-Yes, you are!
I wouldn't be your agent if
I didn't believe in you 100 percent.
You're one of a kind.
Trust me, I know.
Okay, okay...
They're in panic mode.
So make sure you nail this.
-I've got another meeting, so...
-I'll send it when I figure it out.
-Okay. Later, then. Bye!
-Bye.
Bye...
Good morning, everyone.
Hope you're all well.
Norway's in the house!
Hello, Norway!
What am I wearing, someone's asking.
I'm happy to tell you.
This sweater I got from... Reely.
It's pure cashmere. I love it.
I often think that, sure...
No, it's not okay for a sweater
to cost this much.
And this cost a lot of money.
Don't tell anyone.
No, but seriously, I'm against that.
But I also feel, like...
why not get one expensive item,
and have it, and love it for years,
rather than buy
20 fast fashion sweaters...
And given the times
we're living in...
you gotta think about the climate,
the environment, and get involved...
And, like, do your bit
for the greater good.
But enough about politics.
Today's five challenges,
are you ready for them?
Yay!
Wow, I'm getting so much love. You're
really into it today. So lovely!
Okay, here are the challenges.
Olive oil. There we go.
Then you give it a good fry.
Vino , some in the pan...
some in the chef's belly.
Then you let the flavors marry.
Smells wonderful.
I don't have a scent effect,
so you'll have to imagine it.
-What do you think? Will it fly?
-Sounds tasty.
It is tasty. It's really tasty.
-Are you okay?
-Am I okay?
Does it seem desperate?
Posting recipes on Instagram
to keep interest alive?
I meant more the fact that you're
downing cooking wine at 11 a.m.
I need to try and
keep people interested
so they'll come back
once this blows over.
I'm trying to...
get my message out there.
-And your message is...?
-My message is...
Eat! Eat nice food!
I don't fucking know...
I barely got the menus out
before I had to collect them.
Honey? I get a real craving
looking through your feed.
-For what?
-For... food.
-For the food you talk about.
-And maybe for the cook, a little?
And for the cook, a little.
And for his cock?
-Right. So, how was your trip, okay?
-Yes, I took a taxi straight to HQ.
-Talked to your mom yet?
-I will.
-How are the kids?
-What kids?
-They're fine.
-I miss them.
Are you... taking a bath?
Yes, I am.
It looks luxurious.
Trying to relax
before the next meeting.
-Are you naked?
-No, I'm fully clothed.
-Why are you fully clothed?
-It's a good question.
Why would I be fully clothed
in the tub?
-Dunno. That would be a sick fetish.
-Are the kids there? Can I say hi?
Bosse? Lilly?
Mom wants to talk to you.
I don't have time now.
They seem to be busy
with something much more important.
Okay. All right, well,
I'll talk to you later.
I love you.
-Love you guys.
-Kiss.
The orca.
A highly social mammal that actively
interacts and hunts in groups.
The participation of all members
is essential and
fundamental to survival.
Unlike other species, female orcas
are dominant in their society.
And the bond between the female
and her offspring
is described as unique.
However,
this bond will eventually weaken.
Once the young orca reaches maturity,
it'll go its own way...
-What?
-"What?"
What kind of way is that
to answer your mother when she calls?
-What do you want?
-To see you.
Why?
Because I've missed you.
Because you're nice to look at.
I'm nice to look at?
-Hey, I'm your mother.
-Whatever.
I'd rather be interesting
than nice to look at.
They're not mutually exclusive,
are they?
Did you know that orcas are the
most social animals on the planet?
No, I did not know that, actually.
They tactically hunt in pods
where everyone participates.
-And it's vital to their survival.
-Okay...
The bond between mother
and daughter is extremely strong.
It doesn't break until
the daughter leaves the mother
for a new group of likeminded.
And that usually ends
with the mother dying alone.
Okay...
-What?
-No, nothing.
Just... a lot to take in.
Felicia...
Do you feel I've abandoned you?
I'm talking about orcas, Mom.
You know I'm here if you feel alone.
-What do you mean? Dad's here.
-I mean...
I mean alone in a...
How would you describe it?
Like, in your soul.
What are you, drunk?
-What kind of question is that?
-You make zero sense.
I'm just trying to be a little
existential... and sensitive.
Anyway...
I think I'm gonna go shower now.
Okay...
So, I'll check in later?
We'll talk some more about this.
-Take care.
-Okay.
Get the fuck out of my life.
I don't need you anymore.
Two, I fucking hate you,
you fucking bitch.
And three, fuck you! Fuck...
What the... hell?
-Hi!
-Hi.
-What are you doing?
-I'm doing a thing here.
-Can I call you back later?
-Doing anything fun?
I can't talk to my best friend
for, like, two seconds? I need it.
Something happen?
No, nothing in particular,
except that I'm... about to lose it.
I've exhausted Netflix, HBO, Viaplay,
Hulu. I have seen... everything.
My brother got me to watch
The Sopranos  .
-Awesome show.
-Awesome show? It's 86 episodes!
That's 86 hours of my life!
It's like...
86 hours.
And I've filled five bags
with clothes to sell.
Trying to clear out,
make it nice here.
Feels a bit pointless, but... yeah.
I'm trying to, like, think ahead.
-I've ordered new cushion covers.
-Yeah...
I think the pattern is, like,
Japanese.
You know, magnolia trees?
-Igor?
-Yeah?
Hello? I'm talking to you. Igor?
-Igor!
-Yeah, send me a pic later.
You know what? Just... call me later.
Sorry, I'm just super late
with a self-tape here and...
This... could be it.
Sofie's said the US called and said,
"We love this guy."
But, yeah, they're also Americans
and promise you fortunes...
Good luck with that. I'll try and
beat some idiot at Wordfeud and...
Sorry, I suck right now. Later, okay?
Bye.
What scares you the most?
That he lets her sit in front of the
computer all day. That scares me.
Do you know the things
that happen online?
No. Tell me.
What do you mean, tell you...?
I can't tell you everything
that happens there.
But I can tell you this much, it's
not exactly facts making the rounds.
People's theories become her truth.
You know what they're like at that
age. They're like sponges.
I can't connect with her.
Right. What does her father say?
He's such a fucking dumbass.
Or, he's not stupid, but he's...
What to call it? Emotionally
retarded. I can't talk to him.
But... did you feel that way
when you lived together, too?
Or is this a later thing
that came after the divorce?
The man could not be
more validation-seeking.
-He needed validation all the time.
-Yeah...
We're talking about my daughter's
depression, not my separation.
But she has not been diagnosed,
has she?
She never has time to talk,
she has no friends.
If I ask her how she is, she gives me
stats on environmental degradation.
I'll diagnose this thing right here:
she's depressed.
Okay...
What makes you happy, Sofie?
Well... what the hell makes people
happy?
What makes you happy?
Well, that's not... quite how
our relationship is supposed to work.
But...
if you close your eyes...
and think about what makes you...
really, really happy and joyous.
Close your eyes.
What are you thinking about?
No...
Yes, come on! What's going on
in your head right now, Sofie?
I don't know.
Okay... it's fine.
-Flisan!
-Felicia!
Snack time.
Hang on, Mom.
Ow!
Damn!
So hot...
Ow! Ow, ow, ow.
-Felicia?
-What?!
Come out and have a snack with me?
Why?
Could be good
to hang out with people.
You're always
in front of the computer.
Felicia?
I'll leave it outside your door,
have it if you feel like it.
Ow! Shit!
You could've said it was hot!
There. Now I'm here, Mom.
Have you called John?
Was it nice getting a rest?
How is Felicia?
-Fine.
-Is she?
Yeah. Want me to read to you?
Are things good
between the two of you?
-Yes, Mom.
-Let me talk to her?
-Felicia?
-God, what?!
Can you call Grandma on the computer?
-Why?
-Because she wants to talk to you.
I don't feel like talking to her.
You call up Grandma on the computer
right this minute!
Hi, Grandma.
Hi, honey. How are you?
Well, the planet's never been better.
Or, it was better 300 years ago,
before we learned
to destroy everything beautiful.
Be happy you'll soon
be spared this crap.
Sounds like you've been listening
a bit too much to Greta.
-There are no...?
-Greta is milquetoast.
fucking lousy, crappy...
-Dad, we can see you.
-What?
I think this was
the planet's way of going,
"Stop! Look what you're doing to me?"
"I'm on fire!" So we'll stop thinking
so much about ourselves.
PREGNANT
I think it's so important,
to practice self-care in order
to care for others. It's crucial.
So why not just take
ten minutes each day
and pamper yourself,
have some proper me-time,
some quality time with yourself,
and do something good...
and that feels nice.
This moisturising face mask is
absolutely amazing. I'm obsessed.
And it could be yours.
Well, not this exact one,
hanging on my face. A bit gross.
But... I have another one.
So write why you want one of these
in my feed, and I'll send it to you.
What I like most about this one,
if I'm totally honest,
compared to like oxygen...
Sunvacation67
ARE YOU PREGNANT? /DAD
Ossian
LOL, FUNNIEST THING ALL DAY!
-Hey!
-Dad just outed my pregnancy.
To my 200,000 followers.
-He did what now?
-Dad. Our dad.
-He wrote on your blog?
-In all caps. Just shouting it out.
How did he find your blog?
He couldn't even find his way home
from the store 28 years ago.
-Do you realise what this means?
-Um...
-That he's back?
-That I'm going to lose my sponsors.
I'm fucked. I've been hiding
my pregnancy for eight months.
If my followers realise
I'm preggo now, I'm out of a job.
Single mom and unemployed.
Perfect! Nicely done!
-Yeah...
-Really. Fuck.
No one will want to pay
for a mommy vlog.
Okay, but can we back up
for a second,
and talk about our dad being
back from the grave 28 years later?
And shouts on my feed! What the fuck?
What the hell!
I thought he was gonna stay gone.
No, he's back, all right. He's
back... What the hell do I do now?
You've wanted to quit your
influencer career for five years.
Maybe this was the nudge you needed?
So I should be grateful? Thank Dad
for pushing me over the edge?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I'm not worried about you
or your career, Vida.
I'm more worried about having
our dad Allan back in our lives.
Shit!
Now I need to email sunvacation67
and go, "What the hell, Dad?"
-That is not what he's called!
-Sunvacation67, that's his username.
-Ugh, I cannot!
-I can't!
Shit...
Where are you?
I'm on a business trip to Madrid.
-There are still flights going there?
-Not many, but some.
So you have to be in Spain, right
now, for work? Sounds a bit intense.
It is intense, let me tell you.
Yeah...
Fuck. I need to clean up this mess...
and like, take a dump.
But I'll call you later.
Keep me posted.
-On what?
-On... both of those things.
Ugh! okay! Later!
Love you, bye.
What the hell...
Hi, Vida.
It made me so...
happy... when I realised
you were pregnant.
Hello, Vida!
That's so great that you're pregnant!
No...
Vida...
Congratulations.
I think of Igor.
-Allan?
-Yes.
-Hi.
-I think of Igor.
When I close my eyes,
I think of Igor.
I think of his...
...passion for acting.
I think of his eyes.
The pull of his eyes.
And he's so...
He's so fragile.
So frail.
So... unspoiled, in a way.
Yeah...
I realise this is totally sick.
No, it's not sick.
What would be sick about it?
I mean...
The two of you work very closely.
You finally found a guy with a big...
-What?
-...talent.
And you want to help him
with his career.
That's just your job.
Yeah... No, but...
I think about him more than I should.
I absolutely do.
Yes, but... as long as your thoughts
are under control,
and you don't act on them, you're
free to think and feel what you want.
No one can blame you for that.
Neither should you, Sofie.
-Don't be so hard on yourself.
-He's 24 years old.
-And my client.
-Yeah, okay...
-No...
-But it's healthy.
It's perfectly healthy
having taboo thoughts.
-Everyone has them. It's fine.
-Yeah...
-As long as they stay in here.
-Thanks, Allan.
-We have an appointment on Thursday?
-Yes.
Great, I'll speak to you then.
Thank you, bye.
"The world had collapsed ages ago."
"That was a fact."
"But now,
another disaster was looming."
"Perhaps also a rebirth for some,
but not for him."
"Not this time."
"He walked up to the window
and the sun hit his face."
"The light caressed his eyelids
and..."
"suddenly his heart was
somewhat lighter."
Is it supposed to be so...
incomprehensible?
Yes. Or... what do you mean
by incomprehensible?
It's... I...
I'm writing in a new genre.
You need a bit of time,
I'm trying to use other...
-other brushstrokes.
-I don't get what you're saying.
I'm trying to use other brushstrokes,
ways, words to express myself.
Hey, how is Sofie?
-She's fine, I guess.
-Uh-huh?
-Dad?
-Yes?
Is your network down?
-No.
-Can you reboot the network?
-Can't you do something else instead?
-Like what?
Read a book!
You're in there all the time.
You'll get depressed.
Says the man reading a novel he'll
never publish to his dying mother.
Hey!
Ow!
Claes?
-Where were we?
-She's right, you know.
-About the book?
-No, about you.
No, she's not.
This isn't my first time writing.
I'm just choosing to use new words.
I'm trying to be a bit more poetic.
I get to use new words and
try to find something new, don't I?
I'm trying to find something new,
damn it!
I'll hand in the manuscript
when I'm good and ready.
Yes... honey...
You should get a haircut.
-Okay. Okay, Mom...
-And your beard.
You look too shaggy.
You've never tried wearing contacts?
You should meet someone new
before it's too late...
for you too.
I mean, we're all headed that way.
-What do you want me to say?
-Nothing.
Then why would you say such things?
Just tell me what you want me to say!
Your father was also a crier.
HI, DAD
WHO THE FUCK DO YOU THINK YOU ARE
SHOWING UP AFTER 28 YEARS
DO YOU HAVE NOTHING BETTER TO DO?
NO.
STOP BOTHERING ME.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
YES. I DO.
What the hell...
What?
-Why isn't she wearing overpants?
-Hurry up, Lilly!
-Because it's spring.
-It's freezing out.
Has something happened?
Why, because I want my child
to wear weather-appropriate clothes?
No, because your attitude is super
rotten. What's with you?
Why do you need to go out?
Can't you just stay in?
To get some fresh air.
Get some sunshine.
Get some vitamin D.
The sun's good for vitamin D, right?
So is the drugstore.
You can get vitamin D supplements.
Bosse, put this on. We're going
out back for some sunshine.
Then the park so they get to play
for two seconds and I get to breathe.
Then we'll walk the short way back.
Should I bundle her up like it's
winter in the middle of summer?
It's not summer, John!
It's early spring!
Sure, go ahead. If you want
to risk her getting a cold...
What am I risking?
Should she wear a life vest,
a helmet, a gas mask, a wet suit?
Aren't you super busy with work?
Bosse! Shoes!
-Yes. So I need to hang up.
-Hey, before you go!
Our credit card points will expire
if we don't use them now.
Bosse, shoes.
-Okay.
-What do you mean, okay?
Okay, what? Do we use them or not?
-I don't know.
-What don't you know?
It's easy. Either we book now and get
it free or we wait a few months...
And I end up paying for four people.
Booking a holiday now
seems imprudent.
Or super prudent. If we wanna go to
Italy, why don't we just book it?
And if this thing drags out,
we just cancel and that's it.
Bosse! Put your shoes on now!
-Lilly! Finish pooping!
-Piss! Poo!
Hello? You still there?
-I don't know!
-What don't you know?
-If you're still there?
-If booking a holiday is a good idea.
-Daddy! Come!
-The guy keeps emailing me.
I've emailed you several times.
Hey, why don't you answer?
You email me a thousand times a day!
I have a job to do!
-The guy is fucking relentless.
-You don't need to answer now, right?
Yes, I do.
I do need to answer him now.
The world doesn't stop because
you're at a conference in Madrid.
I'm done pooping!
You don't wanna go?
Last year was great.
You told me, book this house
right away for next year.
-What's the deal? Don't you want to?
-Summer vacation is months away.
What's the rush?
Can't we just keep our options open?
If we don't book the house now,
we'll lose it.
-Fuck!
-Daddy! Daddy!
That's... just how it is.
-I need to deal with Lilly now.
-Come on!
Bosse, put your shoes...
-Hey!
-Remember Ossian from Skarpnäck?
Ossian, whose mom our dad
fucked on Walpurgis Night?
fucked on Walpurgis Night.
Vaguely. I mean,
I remember the incident, but not him.
-Okay. Well, anyway, he is a troll.
-What?
-He's a troll?
-He's a troll.
Not the kind of troll
that lives in the woods.
Okay. So where does he live?
Online. He's stalking me,
saying disturbing things.
-Just being an asshole.
-So block him.
But it makes me so mad.
Why act like that?
It's very easy to get all cocky
behind a keyboard.
-You would know.
-Are you going start, too?
Do you think I think it's fun
being 38 years old and, like...
-...an influencer.
-So why are you one?
Not everyone has had it
as easy as you, Matilda.
-You think I've had it easy?
-No, okay, but like, get off my back!
I wasn't attacking you, I just...
God, your claws are really out.
-No, I'm sorry, I'm just...
-Hormonal?
No. No, I'm angry.
I just find it so depressing.
Where are all the sweet guys?
Guys that want to talk or...
dunno, tell a joke, make you laugh,
play guitar until you fall asleep.
-Where are those guys?
-They don't exist.
-No, maybe they don't exist.
-No.
-I don't have time for this BS.
-No! You really don't.
You're gonna be a mom, Vida. Focus on
that instead of some online idiot.
-You don't have time for immaturity.
-No, I really don't.
Next time he gets in touch,
you tell him, "Fuck, leave me alone."
Okay? "Fuck, leave me alone?"
That's what I tell him?
That's super mature and cool.
We'll start with a short overview
of where we are in this pandemic.
More cases by the day. 417,000 cases
worldwide. 20,000 have died.
-I've sent it off.
-Was it okay?
Absolutely. It was more than okay.
Great, so...
Yup. I'll let you know as soon as
they...
I'll let you know as soon as
I hear back from them.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
Hey, so... how are you doing?
How are you... and stuff?
How I am? Should I...?
Or, what do you mean?
No, I was just thinking...
-Talk to you later. It'll be great.
-Yeah. Okay. Cool.
Or I was thinking more, like,
if you...
If you're feeling alone and stuff?
We're living through
such strange times.
And, yeah...
I was thinking that if you...
Just so you know, I'm here if you...
need someone to talk to.
Yeah, definitely, that's cool. My
friend's calling, I need to get this.
Yes, sure thing. I just want you
to know, I'm here for you.
-If you want...
-Yeah. Thanks.
If there's another self-tape,
just send it through.
Because, well, all I have is... time.
Okay, later!
-Bye.
"The new potatoes had tasted like
paper and she was not beautiful."
"But she was kind."
"'Did your life turn out the way
you'd imagined?' he'd asked her."
"'No,' she replied. 'Yours?'"
"'Well... I have been loved.'"
When I woke up,
he had curled up by my feet.
But I kicked him down.
He's in the bathroom now.
He's in the sink.
I can see him through the mirror.
-Who?
-The cat.
The cat, Claes.
Imagine never having been loved.
Shall I go on reading to you?
Are you loved, Claes?
-It's not about that, is it?
-What's it about, then?
The main character is a narcissist.
He craves validation.
Grown people shouldn't run around
expecting love.
Going on about being loved.
You are supposed  to  love.
-What, just straight into the void?
-You should not expect love.
Oh, yes, honey.
You absolutely should.
And if you don't get love...
-...you should leave.
-Sofie was the one that left.
-Is it her you're writing about?
-Cut it out!
Love isn't something you're
supposed to deserve, is it?
Children shouldn't have to
deserve love. Adults, yes.
-Did you have to do that as a child?
-No.
The point is, with adults,
you need to deserve...
you need to work for it.
Oh? Aren't we all children?
No, Mom. We're not.
Shall I read to you?
No. I'm going to get some rest.
Okay.
-I'll call you later?
-Call John.
Claes, honey, call your brother.
Bye, Mom.
Of course...
WHEN YOUR DAD OUTS
YOUR PREGNANCY ONLINE!!!
-Hello?
-Fuck, leave me alone.
Uh, say what now?
Who do you think you are?
What are you doing?
-Wait, didn't you just call me?
-You know I can report you for this?
-Report what?
-A... personal attack.
You're a fucking troll.
You're a troll.
You're an internet troll.
How old are you anyway?
I'm 42. How old are you?
I'm 38... or, it's not...
None of your business.
Okay, I happen to know you're 38.
I was asking to be polite.
Just... leave me alone.
-Stay away.
-Will do.
Can I just ask you, out of curiosity,
isn't this just what you strive for?
More followers, more likes,
more engagement?
I helped you indirectly. You've got
more followers now than this morning.
I don't want any help
from a dirty internet troll.
-Okay.
-Okay?
I don't want people in my life
who are there to be mean.
I don't want it around me.
-That was not my intention.
-Right.
Okay? That was not my intention
at all. I thought it was funny.
You are funny.
I follow your livestream.
I don't think it's funny
that you watch my livestream.
Okay. Your dad reaching out maybe
wasn't well thought out, but Jesus...
He's of a different generation.
Right? He didn't know it would turn
into such a huge thing for you.
He was just trying to get in touch.
-Unfollow me, please.
-You got it.
-Great.
-Bye.
Okay...?
Hey? Breathe. Hey? Hey, hey?
Listen, we're gonna be able to go
back to our lives in a week or so.
Okay?
Look at me. I'm here.
I'm just a screen away.
Fuck, I look like shit.
Plus, I feel really ugly.
-I'm sorry.
-No...
I'm sorry I call you all the time.
Don't say that. Always call me.
Always!
Yeah, but I know you're busy
working on your self-tapes...
You're working so hard,
and I don't want to bother you...
But I just feel super, super afraid.
Like, this... isn't me!
This isn't... I'm not... This isn't
me, this isn't me, to be like this.
I know.
Hey, you know...
You know what I think?
No, tell me what you think.
I think... or I'm thinking...
things happen around you
all the time.
An event, an inauguration,
a club, and there's...
a ton of people around you
all the time.
Every time I see you,
you're either coming or going.
There's nothing wrong with you.
You're just...
really bad at being alone.
Yeah...
I wish you were here.
I wish I was there.
We could pop some popcorn.
-Watch Crazy, Stupid, Love.
-Yeah...
You really have a special fondness
for bad movies.
You've seen it, right?
No, but I've seen every other film
you recommended.
Wait. You haven't seen
Crazy, Stupid, Love ?
-As I was saying...
-It's actually good.
We need to watch it.
Do you have popcorn at home?
-Do you have popcorn?
-Let me check.
-Yes!
-Good.
I've got popcorn. Let's watch this.
HI VIDA,
I'D LIKE TO GET IN TOUCH WITH YOU.
DO YOU HAVE A PHONE NUMBER?
LOVE, YOUR DAD ALLAN
SAME NUMBER I'VE HAD
SINCE I GOT A CELLPHONE
What the hell is the message?
This is your favourite movie?
-Hello?
-Wait, wait. Listen to this email.
-What?
-"Want to read for Sofia Coppola?"
-Who's that?
-Do I want to read for Sofia Coppola?
"If you like the material,
please put yourself on tape,"
"for Sergei, the male stripper,
by tomorrow morning."
-Did you say, "male stripper?"
-Sofia Coppola!
-Holy shit!
-You can't do that.
Sofia Coppola, Hanna?
Do you not know who she is?
Male stripper? Are you nuts?
I'm sorry, let me call you later.
I need to get working on this.
-What?
-I'm sorry. I'll explain later. Bye.
Hello?
-Hello?
-Hi, Vida.
-Hi...
Dad. Allan.
I've tried to reach you.
Yeah... I've noticed.
I'm not that great with technology.
No... I've noticed that, too.
How are you?
I'm sorry, but why
do you want to know?
Because I'm your father.
Oh, shit, yeah... that's you.
Because I care about you.
You have an odd way of showing it.
Going to the store to get the paper,
and showing up 28 years later.
By shouting out I'm pregnant
on my feed.
I don't understand what you mean.
What do you mean? How's that?
I've lived my whole life
without a dad.
I'm doing well. I'm fine.
I don't know if I have time...
for you.
-Right, I understand.
-Good.
Are you pregnant?
I'm with child, yes.
I'm expecting a child.
My God, Vida...
You're expecting a child.
You don't care about your children,
or your grandchildren, at all.
So it just feels a bit weird,
for you to suddenly...
I... don't have time for this.
No, I get that.
I suppose you have a busy life.
But I was just thinking that maybe,
at some point...
If you'd like to... meet.
No. No...
No...
Okay.
All right, well, it was fun...
Well, I don't know about fun...
But it was nice...
seeing you this way, at least.
It's something.
-Goodbye.
I love children
with the whole of my heart...
And we need to remember
this is just the tip of an iceberg.
Many more are infected
in different parts of the world.
An indication of something that is
slowly spreading across the world.
People have been good. Far
fewer people are out in Stockholm.
Things are progressing quite calmly,
with several countries
in the same phase.
But people need to understand
we need to keep this up.
We can't stop.
Stay home if you're showing symptoms.
And we must protect the elderly.
Hello?
-Hello?
-Uh...
Hello? I don't know...
I don't know if I called...
No, it was me who called you.
I called you.
-I called you.
-Okay...?
I don't know... I don't think
you have the right number.
-My name is John...
-I know.
I'd like to speak to Bosse and Lilly.
What, why...
do you wanna talk to them?
Because I'm their grandfather.
Matilda's father.
Okay...
I don't really know if...
-Bosse? Lilly?
-What?
Your...
Grandpa wants to talk to you.
Han Solo and Leia
are Kylo Ren's parents.
And Luke is Kylo Ren's uncle.
Oh, wow. That sounds complicated.
-You know what, though?
-What?
Darth Vader is also
Kylo Ren's grandfather.
Oh, wow, grandfather? Just like me.
Yeah. But then he uses all his Jedi
powers so that Rey will live.
And then he dies. Bye!
Here, Lilly.
-Who are you?
-I am your grandfather.
Mom says we don't have a grandfather.
Honey, everyone has
a grandfather somewhere.
-Not me.
-Oh, Lilly!
You are a piss-poo!
Lilly! Give me the phone now!
You have got to be kidding me!
What was I supposed to do?
He wanted to talk to them.
-Why?
-Because he's their grandfather.
-Should I have told him he couldn't?
-Um, yeah!
Okay, well... but I didn't.
He has no right showing up
after all these years,
out of nowhere, and talk to  my  kids.
Your kids? They're our kids.
-They don't even know who he is.
-No, and they made that clear to him.
-Did she say he was a poo?
-She may have called him, I dunno...
What was it? A piss-poo?
-Wow, she's really coughing.
-No, she isn't.
-John... I can hear her coughing.
-She is not coughing, honey.
She's choked on food or is scratchy.
She's not coughing, she's not sick.
Okay, wait, hello? If she's choked
on something, maybe check on her?
I'm here looking at her.
She's not blue, she can breathe,
she's not dying or sick.
-Have you checked her temperature?
-She does not have a temperature.
Let me see her.
-Lilly!
-Hi Mommy.
Hi, honey! Okay, she looks
boiling hot. Take her sweater off.
Honey, please! You wanted her
to get bundled up before going out.
-You went outside again?!
-I had to get groceries!
They can't be left here,
because you're not here.
-Nice. You wanna put that on me too?
-God...
Do you think I enjoy being here?
It's not my choice. I had to come.
John! John?
-What about the house in Italy?
-I think we should wait.
Wait for what? For better times?
A more fun family to vacation with?
-I think it's stupid to book now.
-You think... All right, fine.
You know what? Fuck it.
I'm just trying to organise
some fun things for this family.
But if you want to take the lead
on this, go ahead. I give up.
-Great. Thanks.
-Bye.
I'm all dirty!
Hi, girls.
Or, I'm sorry.
You're no longer girls.
It's just that I think a lot
about when you were kids.
What things were like back then.
How you were.
I remember that you, Matilda,
were very precocious.
You were really sharp.
You were first kid on the block to...
learn how to ride a bike, swim...
You ran faster than anybody.
You were really... great.
And you...
Vida, you weren't quite as...
You took your time a bit more,
learning things...
But when you were born, and became
part of the family, that's when...
You were an incredibly lively
little whirlwind, running around.
Yeah, it was really...
It was...
It was really...
nice.
Shit...
I can't do this.
If you want me to stop, just tell me.
"Imagine getting to experience
falling in love again."
"An intense desire."
"Unlike the love of marriage,
en passant."
"Something uncertain,
sharp as a knife's edge."
"New."
"Life."
Are you enjoying this?
"The kids' whining and screaming
had pushed out the thoughts."
"But this week was hers."
"It was too early for bed,
but too late to get drunk."
"If the priority was to forget."
"He poured some disinfectant and
mixed with the kids' leftover juice."
Okay...
-Hello?
-Hi.
-Who is this?
-Who is it?
It's your brother. It's Claes.
-Wow.
-Yeah...
Have you called Mom?
-Should I?
-Um, yes...
They've moved her to
a palliative ward.
-Okay?
-You do know what "palliative" means?
Um, yes, Claes,
I know what "palliative" means.
So call her, then!
What's with your shitty tone?
Did I do something to you?
Mom's illness isn't news.
She's been sick a while now.
So what, you don't need to call her?
-Or what are you trying to say?
-What?
What are you trying to say?
That you don't need to call her?
-Did I say that? What's with you?
-You don't care!
You just float on the surface.
"It's all good."
-You're like Teflon.
-Teflon, what...?
Teflon does not float on the surface.
What you fry in Teflon does. God.
Everything is
so fucking easy for you.
-What do you know about it?
-You're not discreet.
I have Instagram.
Okay,
Instagram may miss a few things.
Like the fact that your wife
probably is about to leave you.
What's that?
I think my wife is leaving me, Claes.
Fuck. I didn't know.
-No, you didn't.
-Sorry.
-Want a little tip?
-Uh... no?
Stop feeling so sorry for yourself.
The world doesn't revolve around you.
Here's a little tip for you.
Are you listening?
Fuck off!
But call Mom first.
I don't understand
why you just won't ask for help.
If life is so hard for you,
why not just ask for help?
Okay.
Help.
-Help? Help you with what?
-Help me.
-With what?
-Help!
Taking you to the barber,
shaving your beard? What?
-Call Mom!
-Goddamn...
I'm not gonna be able to sit with you
after she's died.
Hearing about how sad you are, how
much you regret not talking to her.
-Call Mom!
-Claes...
You're the last person I'm going to
call when I get sad. Now you know.
It is what it is.
I'VE DECIDED TO TAKE A BREAK.
TAKE CARE OF EACH OTHER.
KISS.
DO YOU NEED SOMEONE TO TALK TO?
I PROMISE TO BE NICE
Hi.
No, I kept track of you until,
like, the end of 8th grade.
-When we moved to the city.
-The city? okay.
Yup... when did you move?
-I'm still here.
-No shit?
-Yes.
-Where?
No, of course not.
I live in Södermalm.
It's not unreasonable
to still be living in Skarpnäck.
Beloved Skarpnäck...
-Such great memories from there.
-You do?
Good for you. I don't.
Okay...
You know your mom and my dad fucked
on Walpurgis Night 28 years ago?
I know that's what the neighbours
were saying, but it's not true.
Wait... how would you know that?
-Because I know.
-How can you say it's not true?
Because I know! My parents
stayed happily married all along.
Mom and Dad never liked that area.
So much gossip and bullshit.
It was like living
in an episode of Dynasty.
Skarpnäck, the Dynasty of Stockholm?
I don't know...
That's a good one. Deserves a top-ten
spot of county slogans.
Listen to this one:
"Alnön - the Hawaii of the North."
And this is a good one:
"Flen - a county."
Why are you so angry at your dad?
If I may ask?
You may ask.
Because he left me and my sister...
and my mother, for another woman.
-For your mother.
-Except, that's not what happened.
But that's what I've believed
until now.
-So if that's false, then...
-Which it is. It's false.
It doesn't matter. It's not about the
infidelity, it's about the betrayal.
One day, I have a dad. The next...
I don't know, it really affects you,
let me tell you.
It changed life completely.
-I can understand that.
-How do you even do that?
Leave your kids?
My mother was... devastated.
My sister has dealt with her
aggression issues in her own...
kooky ways.
How?
She has just erased him.
He doesn't exist to her anymore.
Okay. What about you?
Well...  now  I'm okay.
But it was rough. I was ten years
old, I was in fourth grade, so I...
I took on all the blame myself.
I thought I'd done something wrong.
Hm... Have you asked your dad
why he did what he did?
No, I haven't. Because no matter
what the answer is, it's not okay.
-No...
-No.
Be good to get an explanation,
perhaps?
Would you want an explanation?
Get some closure, maybe?
-No, I don't know...
-Me neither.
-Do you play?
-Basketball?
-No, I mean... the guitar.
-Oh.
-No, I dabble.
-So play for me.
I don't know.
We're not quite there yet, are we?
-Come on!
-No. No...
So, what do you do...
when the world is coming to an end?
HOW ARE YOU?
How am I doing?
Hang on, let me get a read...
Yeah, I'm doing good.
And if you ask me tomorrow,
I'll feel like shit again!
ARE YOU DRUNK?!?
WAS JUST WONDERING THE SAME THING...
Yes, I'm drunk. I'm allowed.
And I'm a bit hot. I don't know
if I've caught my daughter's fever,
or if it's all the melted cheese
that I've eaten,
which has set
like a nice layer of fat...
I'm getting a call
from my wonderful... Fräulein...
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Good night.
-Does Lilly have a fever?
-Are you watching my live stream?
-Why didn't you comment?
-Does Lilly have a fever?
Yes... she does have a temperature.
Yes.
What the hell, John!
Why didn't you call me and tell me?
What are you gonna do from Madrid?
Make it go away by magic?
Hocus focus, fever jokus - gone!
Why shout it out on your regulars'
forum if you want me in the dark?
Because I didn't think you followed
my dorky food account.
-Is her temperature high?
-You haven't exactly praised it.
-Have you given her paracetamol?
-You realise you're being insane?
-You think I'm being insane?
-Yes.
-Have you called the health line?
-I look after my daughter, honey.
Didn't I tell you not to go out
with the kids? Didn't I?!
You need to stand the fuck down!
Stop backseat-driving me!
Either be here and sort things out,
or be there and shut up
and get the fuck off my back.
I'm on your back
when you're not thinking clearly.
And you're thinking clearly?
Going away for a weekend
during a global crisis?
And my worst life crisis ever? That's
a good time for a weekend trip?
-What was I supposed to do?!
-Prioritise me!
-But...
-Prioritise us!
What are you...? I always
prioritise you, my family! Always!
What do you even mean? I'm falling
apart from prioritising you so much!
You're falling apart because
you prioritise us  and  everyone else.
And  your friends, your job,
colleagues, the shit you're into.
If you prioritise everything,
in the end you prioritise nothing!
Why do you live with a woman who
doesn't prioritise you or her family?
I don't know.
Been asking myself that question.
-Can I see her?
-She's sleeping.
Can I see her when she's sleeping?
-I want to see if she seems hot.
-Stop it.
Let me see my daughter!
You don't get to see your daughter
right now. Bye.
Don't you hang up on me ever again,
John.
You'll get to see your daughter
when you get home.
Good night.
Try to calm down.
What is it that's happened?
Well, I...
Try to be a bit objective, Sofie.
Just tell me the facts
of what happened.
I asked Igor to do a nude scene...
for a director that he admires.
But...
it was really for you.
Wasn't it?
Mm...
-Sofie...
-Yes?
I hope you realise you've subjected
this boy to pretty severe abuse?
He's... a man, first of all.
A young man...
Granted, he's a young man,
but he's not a boy.
-It's not about age.
-Then why bring it up?
You're his agent.
You have his future in your hands.
He'd do pretty much anything for you.
There's a huge imbalance
in your power dynamic.
Wasn't this what the whole Me Too
debate was all about?
Of course I realise
I've crossed a line here.
Otherwise I wouldn't have called you
in the middle of the night, would I?
But it's not abuse!
He doesn't even know about it.
Would he have stripped for you,
had it not been for a part?
Does he really seek you out
like that?
I didn't violate him, if that's
what you're making it out to be.
Those are just poor excuses.
Some people,
you are simply no good for.
Sometimes it's better to just cut
all ties. Not least for their sake.
You're right, actually.
So I'm cutting ties with you right
now. Bye, it's been a good few years.
Okay...
Listen to me.
On Walpurgis Night 28 years ago,
I ended up in bed with the neighbour.
That led to everything turning out
the way it did...
But I want you to understand
it had nothing to do with you girls.
Us getting divorced. I didn't mean
for you kids to suffer for it.
But of course you did.
I let you suffer for it.
And that's something
I just have to...
I've had to live with that,
and that's... that's okay...
What the hell am I...
The thing is...
Here's the...
I'm sick.
I'm sick. Cancer.
It... really is crazy...
Prostate.
It's too far gone,
there's nothing they can do, so I...
That's also an excuse.
I really just wanted to say
that I love you.
Hi, Mom.
Hi, John...
Sorry to call you so late.
Better late than never.
How are you?
-He's here now.
-Who?
-Here in bed...
-Dad?
No. The cat.
Okay...
Okay.
I don't want to die, John.
Who does?
Or, well, I do...
I wouldn't mind dying.
I could trade places with you.
Not have to deal with this shit.
Mom?
I don't have time for this right now.
Oh?
What are you getting up to?
Mom?
John, not now...
Honey...
-If you want me to stop just tell me.
-Yes, stop!
Okay... Listen to me.
On Walpurgis Night 28 years ago,
I ended up in bed with the neighbour.
That led to everything turning out
the way it did...
But I want you to understand
it had nothing to do with you girls.
Us getting divorced. I didn't mean
for you kids to suffer for it.
But of course you did.
I let you suffer for it.
One thing I'm insanely good at,
is throwing things up in the air
and catching them in my mouth.
Things? What...?
I don't mean, like, furniture.
Small things like grapes or...
a nut of some sort, maybe.
-Right.
-A pecan nut.
You can't just drop something like
that on me and not show me?
Yeah, but it's not something
I do on command.
Plus, I need some wine in my system.
So get some wine!
Oh, no, that's right...
-So that means I have to wait...
-Three months.
Stop it.
-What time is it?
-I really need to go to bed now.
Guess I'll have to google
some old busker or something.
Someone that can play for me
since you won't.
I just wanna fall asleep
and wake up to a new,
much better day than this one.
God, you keep going on about it.
And on, and on, and on.
Okay, okay, I'm not gonna let you...
fall asleep to fucking Winnerbäck
or some shit.
-For real?
-Okay, lie down.
I am lying down.
What do I play...
Thank you!
I love you, my dark continent!
I don't understand.
She wouldn't even tell me why.
And she kept telling me, she'd never
met a more natural actor than me.
And you know who she reps.
I mean... I believed in this.
You know what?
You'll find a new agent.
I'm really... so fucking stupid.
How could I be so naive?
You're not naive. You trust people,
what are you gonna do?
That's exactly it. Never trust anyone
other than yourself.
That's, like, the most beautiful
thing you can do!
I'm so stupid.
I'm so fucking stupid.
I thought I was this close...
And now it's just... all over.
Hey...
You'll get a new shot.
Igor, look at me.
You'll get a thousand new shots.
I promise.
Everything is going to be all right.
Mom is... Mom is dead.
Was...
Was she...
Was she in pain?
It's okay to cry.
I know.
You're there and I'm here.
Is there anything I can do for you?
I just want to sit here awhile.
Of course.
Want me to read to you?
I have my latest book here.
Maybe... now's not the time.
Okay.
Hang on, I need to get this.
I need to get this.
-Hey.
-Forgive me, John. I'm so sorry.
-What is it, honey?
-I'm spinning out of control, John.
I can't keep a lid on my emotions.
They just keep boiling over.
-What?
-I just run away from everything.
-And... I can't do this.
-What are you talking about?
What kind of parent
can't stand their own kids?
I think you're better off without me.
What?
What? Where's this coming from?
Did your dad trigger this?
I don't know.
Yes, maybe. I don't know.
-But... there's some truth to it.
-No, there's not. What truth?
I let you guys suffer for it.
I don't want to feel... inadequate.
I don't want to feel like a bad mom.
But right now, I am. Right now,
I'm such a bad fucking mom.
No, you're not.
-I can't do this...
-Yes!
Our kids are...
the most beautiful thing ever.
And they should fucking have
the world's best mom.
They do!
You are the world's best mom.
No...
I think they're a pain in the ass.
That's because they are!
I think so too.
Everyone does. You're not alone
in thinking your kids are a pain!
I don't deserve you guys.
You shouldn't have to deserve love,
honey.
John... please
don't get mad at me now.
Huh?
I'm not on a business trip.
I checked into a hotel
five minutes away from home.
Just to get some peace and quiet.
Honey... did you think I didn't know?
Can't you just come home now?
We need you.
What if the world was,
like, different...
How?
What if this was
a  Sliding Doors  world.
Say you were born in
a totally different country,
into a totally different family.
That you were up at night
and slept during the day.
What if I wasn't me,
and you weren't you.
That we were
totally different people.
Like...
if you were me...
and I was you?
Yeah... for example.
-Yeah, there's a scary thought.
-Yeah...
Seriously, what if we
hadn't become besties?
-If...
-What?
No, I don't know...
What if I'd been
a totally different girl?
Whom I'd be
lying here talking to now?
Yes, except...
You wouldn't be you.
You'd be someone else.
Who'd be lying here talking
to this girl... that's not you?
Yes...
What if that girl...
What?
What if she had feelings that...
she was scared to tell him?
Why... would she be scared
to tell him about those feelings?
Maybe she'd be scared
they wouldn't be mutual?
What if they were?
Yes, but how would she know?
Well, what if...
she did know,
she knew that he had...
been in love with her
and wanted her for a while now?
Would she be scared to tell him
about those feelings then?
No.
In that world...
In that other world...
what if they were together?
Everything would have been totally...
uncomplicated.
Imagine they were in the same room.
In the same bed.
In another world.
In another world,
it would have been nice.
"Enough."
"Comfort could no longer be found
in the darkness."
"Withdrawal would be rough,
he knew that."
"He poured the disinfectant on
the orchid, all she'd left behind."
"Take that, you fucker."
"He tightened his belt
and opened his eyes."
"Finally, daybreak."
Flisan!
Yes?
Grandma died last night.
It was...
It was quiet. It was peaceful. She...
What's the...?
She... died in peace... Peacefully.
Okay. Anything else?
Would you like some breakfast?
Come here, honey.
Why?
I'd like to give you a hug.
I don't want a hug.
What if I need one?
It's okay, honey.
You smell like old man.
You're not exactly the epitome
of freshness, either.
Hi, you've reached Allan.
Leave a message.
Hi, it's me. Matilda.
When all this blows over,
how about you come over for dinner?
I think the kids would appreciate it.
I would, too.
Why don't you call me
when you get this?
Bye, Dad.
We'll start with these, but you
throw them to me. So it's fair.
I'll throw them from here.
You're not as great
as you claim to be.
Wait! It's easier with bigger stuff.
Want me to make you breakfast?
What are you craving?
Bacon...
Eggs...
Bacon and eggs.
Bacon? Bacon and eggs?
You're one of a kind.
Trust me, I know. Read it!
Dad, did you want to have a coffee?
Yes. Soon.
Let me know.
Hi.
-Welcome home.
-Thanks.
-I've missed you.
-I've missed you too.
Okay...
Can't you throw something really big?
-Now you do something.
-You want me to do something?
Yes, play some...
That was so bad.
-Mommy!
-Hi, my darlings!
FOR DAD
Subtitles: Plint
www.plint.com